I feel so elegant with my new Anoasis corset and it's going to get even more elegant because
in this beautiful Anoasis box there's something else I received. A latex catsuit and as always
oh it always smells so good. Oh yeah definitely recommend the Anoasis perfume too
because it's just so good this smell and inside this box there it is the second outfit this
catsuit and the special thing about this catsuit is that there are golden zippers
and also there are shoulder zippers right here and this is the specialty i've never won a shoulder
zipped catsuit before so this is going to be my first time but as you can see I
definitely need to shine this one up because it has a lot of talcum on it so
I'm going to do that now yay first time catsuit with the shoulder zippers for me
this is a premiere because I've never worn such a catsuit and I think it looks
really great the zippers here on the shoulders were easy to get into so easy
to handle easy to dress it's I wasn't used to it but it wasn't problem so you
basically just have to dress the arm from here to here and then close the
zipper all the way up it's easier if you have help with that I'm gonna tell you
that but yeah that's the close-up look and now onto the full body all right I
paired it with boots that have golden zippers too and if you're thinking damn
what are these awesome shoes they're Versace Couture they're not available
anymore and I'm really happy that I found them to combine them especially
with the things with golden zippers and I think it's a great look together I
I also have one of my trusty metal belts which I'm going to add. I think that makes the look complete and what I also love is this V shape here so the seam starts at the shoulders, has the zippers in the middle over the boobs and then goes all the way until it meets the crotch zipper here.
This is a really really cool design feature. I love that. It gives something more extravagant and sophisticated. What's with the backslide? Let's have a look. So classy backslide but also with the golden zipper here up until here it's an eye catcher for sure.
Yes, I like it.
I'm wearing size small and the sizes are available in four different length options.
So I'm wearing the second longest fitting to my size.
I'm 173 centimeters tall.
Now the pros and cons of shoulder zippers.
that I've worn it a bit I am starting to feel that there's pressure here on the
shoulder zip on my shoulder of course if you're wearing a front zip or a back zip
catsuit you have these pressure points on the front or on the back so there is
pressure if it's not a neck entry catsuit there is a point where that pressure is
the fit on the neck is comfortable it is not too tight even though you may wonder about that
because the zippers end here I don't really feel them here so no problem at all and it's really
nice that I can like bend over and move around without having the restriction of a zipper in
my back here so that's a really big plus point anyway I have a discount code for Anoasis
it is valid one month after this video is released and as you saw in the intro they do not only make
latex but also leather outfits which are really cool so you should definitely check everything
out I'll put everything down in the description box we have a crotch zipper which is really handy
if you have to use the bathroom or want to have some fun times the metal zipper does not touch
your skin there is a skin protection which is super nice and last but not least the breast
zippers I can open them for you because I'm wearing a bra underneath for exactly that reason
so you can see they open and are functional so not just for decorative reasons and you can also
So of course just put the citrus here or in the middle or below so you can have different
looks with them.
If you want to see more from Anoasis you can check out my other videos and I just realized
when I said Anoasis that it's not pronounced Anoasis.
They made a video on their Instagram and talked about how to pronounce it and it's Anoises.
I learned that I just completely forgot again because I've been saying anoises for years already.
Sorry, anoises, for saying it wrong all these years.
It is a beautiful name though.
And now, yeah, that was it for today.
I hope you had fun with this video.
Leave a thumbs up.
Check out everything I put in the description text.
And leave a comment.
Tell me, do you have any experience with shoulder zipper catsuits?
and yeah for the end of the video I can open one for you so you can
see that's how I'm going to get undressed now have a nice time bye